let STORE = [
  {
    question:
      "Minecraft has many foodstuffs. Which of these would you not find in a standard game?",
    answers: ["Mushroom Stew", "Popsicles", "Cake", "Apples"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which single action in Minecraft would render you the most experience?",
    answers: [
      "Smashing a Bottle oâ€™ Enchanting",
      "Mining a diamond ore block",
      "Killing a baby zombie",
      "Catching a pufferfish"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which direction does the sunflower always face?",
    answers: ["North", "South", "East", "West"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question:
      "One way to deal damage to mobs is using gravity. Which of these mobs cannot be hurt by falling?",
    answers: ["Silverfish", "Witch", "Wolf", "Iron golem"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question:
      "When silverfish hide in a stone block, the block becomes infested. How many types of blocks can silverfish infest?",
    answers: ["4", "6", "3", "8"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question:
      "Of all the ores, Emerald Ore is the rarest mineral block in the game. It only naturally generates in which biome?",
    answers: ["Extreme hills", "Forest", "Jungle", "Taiga"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the minimum amount of bookshelves required for a level 30 enchantment?",
    answers: ["12", "15", "8", "18"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question:
      "In a standard game of Minecraft, which of these enemies will deal the most damage to the player per hit?",
    answers: ["Zombie Pigman", "Wither", "Enderman", "Blaze"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "What year was Minecraft initially released?",
    answers: ["2012", "2010", "2011", "2009"],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    question:
      "In a standard game of Minecraft, what can you not do in the Nether?",
    answers: [
      "Grow a tree",
      "Place bookshelves",
      "Sleep in a bed",
      "Light a fire"
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }
];
